<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
   <data>
      <template id="terms_and_conditions_hive_2024_turkey">



<table style="width: 100%; font-size: 8pt; text-align: justify; font-weight: bold; border: 1px solid #ffffff;">
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="width: 80.5%;">
<br></br>
<strong>PARTICIPATION AGREEMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS:</strong>
<br></br>
                                        These terms and conditions are to be read as an integral part of the Participation Agreement.
                                        <br></br>
                                        <br></br>
<p style="margin-left:15px">
<strong>  1. DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION </strong>
<br></br>
<br></br>
In these terms and conditions and in the first page of this Participation Agreement, the following words shall have the meaning respectively assigned to them hereunder, unless the context requires or admits otherwise:
<br></br>
<br></br>
    <p style="margin-left:30px">
          1.1. “Agreement” shall mean this Participation Agreement including the first page and the terms and conditions as executed by the Organizer or Exhibitor and includes Schedule A and B attached thereto;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.2. “Applicable Laws” shall mean the local laws and regulations of the Emirates of Dubai and the federal laws of the United Arab Emirates;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.3. “Booth” shall mean the fragmented allocated space(s) measured in square meters within the Exhibition as set up by the Organizer and as allocated to each specific Exhibitor by the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.4. “Center User” shall mean all the exhibitors at all the center, tenants of allocated space, and includes each of their agents, contractor, employees, invitees, and attendees of the Exhibition;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.5. “Exhibition” shall mean the event as named and dated in the Participation Agreement;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.6. “Exhibitor” shall mean the Company mentioned on page 1 of this Agreement and can include any person, ﬁrm, company, association, organization, and its employees, or agents to whom exhibit space has been allocated for the purpose of exhibiting at the Exhibition, represented by the authorized signatory of this Agreement;
       <br></br>
<br></br>
        1.7. “Contracted Term” shall mean the contracted period under the Agreement as speciﬁcally mentioned in the Participation Agreement;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.8. “Exhibitor Manual” shall mean the manual of the Organizer’s internal guidelines established from time to time and distributed to the Exhibitor prior to the Exhibition for the sale and orderly conduct and close of the Exhibition;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.9. “Exhibition Material” shall mean such good, exhibits, materials equipment, stand/s, supplies, merchandise, models, exhibit items, or other property for the sole use of the Exhibition;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.10. “Force Majeure” shall mean any event or circumstances (or a combination of events or circumstances) which are beyond the reasonable control of the relevant  party, resulting in or causing the failure by that party to perform any of its obligation under this Agreement (whether in whole or in part), including without limitation: (1) revolution, riots, insurrection or other civil commotion, act of terrorism or sabotage or war; (2) nuclear explosion, radioactive, biological or chemical contaminations or radiation; (3) general strikes, work stoppages, working to rule, go slow actions and or lockout; (4) any eﬀect of the natural elements including lightening, ﬁre, earthquakes, ﬂood, storm, hurricane, tsunami, cyclone or tornado, materials change in sea level or coastal subsidence; (5) explosion (other than nuclear explosion or any explosion resulting from an act or war); (6) inability to obtain necessary plant, equipment or materials due to blockade, embargo or sanction;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.11. “Insurance Costs” means the cost of the obtaining the mandatory insurance cover as prescribed in clause 12.1 and set out under the particulars;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.12. “Intellectual Property Right” means all intellectual property rights and includes all trademarks, rights to use the logos, rights to use the names and likeness, copyrights, moral rights, rights in databases, confidential information and any rights, interest or forms of protection of a similar nature, including without limitation, all economic and exclusive rights to reproduce, fix, adapt, modify, translate, create derivative works from, introduce into circulation, publish, distribute, sell, license, sublicense, transfer, transmit or provide access electronically, broadcast, display, enter into computer memory, or otherwise use any portion or copy, in whole or in any form, directly or indirectly, or to authorize or assign others to do so having equivalent or similar effect to any of them which subsist anywhere in the world, in all cases whether or not registered or registrable and including registrations and applications for registration or grant of any of these and rights to apply for the same;

<br></br>
<br></br>



        1.13. “Marketing Powerpack Cost” means (where applicable) the cost of the powerpack or enhances internet listing. If any provided by the exhibitor as set out in the clause 12.3 and the particulars;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.14. “Objectionable Displays” shall mean any signage, products, services or show performance or literature could be considered oﬀensive, immoral, contrary to the Applicable Laws, or is politically or socially to Dubai or the U.A.E or their relations with other countries, trade bodies, associations, clients or is otherwise objectionable in the sole and discretionary opinion of the Organizer;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.15. "Offerings" Booth set up offerings as provided by OMG to finalized Exhibitors and as listed in Schedule B attached hereto which may include stand set-up, fit-out, power supply, carpet, lights, shipment, hotel, furniture assembly assistance, etc.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.16. “Organizer” shall mean the OMG Exhibition Organizing;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.17. “Organizer Marks” shall mean all trademarks, service marks, logos, commercial symbols, or indicia together with the other trading names and styles and such other related and ancillary marks which are proprietary marks of or controlled by OMG in any form, manner, font, color, and size as prescribed/authorized/ permitted by OMG from time to time.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.18. “Refund” shall mean by way of bank transfer or credit note, which shall be issued on such terms and conditions as deemed reasonable by the Organizer, considering all relevant surrounding circumstances at such the acting in a good faith manner, in this regard, the Organizer shall serve the right, acting in its reasonable discretion, to deduct direct cost actually and reasonably incurred in order to organize the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.19. “Permitted Activities” shall mean conducting certain activities limited to exhibiting and selling furniture products and any other activities as allowed by the Organizer at the Venue during the Event Days.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.20. “Registration Fees” shall mean the fee set out under the particulars.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.21. “Total Exhibition Fee” shall mean the sum payable by the Exhibitor to the Organizer in the amount and manner set out in Schedule A to these terms and conditions (and the avoidance of doubt shall include the Insurance costs, Registration Fee and Marketing Powerpack Costs and/or Enhanced Internet Listing);
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.22. “VAT” means value added tax or sales tax and any other tax of a similar nature imposed in any jurisdiction; and
<br></br>
<br></br>
        1.23. “Venue” shall mean the location for the Exhibition as mentioned on the first page of this Participation Agreement or as maybe modified by OMG and communicated to Exhibitor.

<br></br>




    </p>















</p>

<p style="margin-left:15px">
    <strong>   2. USE AND ALLOCATION OF SPACE </strong>
    <br></br>
  <p style="margin-left:30px">


        2.1. The Exhibitor has sought permission from the Organizer and hereby agrees to conduct the Permitted Activities as allowed by the Organizer at the Venue on the Event Date subject to the payment of Total Exhibition Fee set out in this Agreement and the Organizer has agreed to grant such permission in accordance with the terms and conditions contained herein. The Organizer hereby allots a designated Booth size as set out on page 1 of this Agreement to the Exhibitor at the Exhibition for the purpose of the Exhibitor to conduct the Permitted Activities on the Event Dates. The Exhibitor may choose to avail one of the packages as below: (a) Booths without Offerings or Booths along-with Offerings. Fee for both shall be set out in Schedule A..
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.2. The Exhibitor undertakes to exhibit under the brand name as listed on the first page of this Agreement and the Exhibitor undertakes that this brand is owned or controlled solely by the Exhibitor.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.3. Parking on Event Days: During the Event Days, the Exhibitor acknowledges that the guests of the Exhibitor would be accommodated on first come first serve basis.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.4. The Exhibitor shall not violate the rules and regulations of the Venue. The Exhibitor shall ensure that during the use of the Venue, no damage will be caused to the Venue or property of the Organizer and/or the Venue and no hindrance of any nature will be caused to any of the activities of the Venue.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.5. The Exhibitor and any person duly appointed by the Exhibitor undertake to:
<br></br>
<br></br>
      <p style="margin-left:45px">

          2.5.1. Comply with the safety measures imposed by the Applicable Laws and regulations during set-up, break-down of the units throughout the Exhibition, and
<br></br>
<br></br>
            2.5.2. Be present at their Booth's and/or assigned location, solely for reasons related to set-up and break-down, as well as during the inspection by the Organizer for ensuring compliance with safety standards.

      </p>
            <br></br>
            <br></br>
        2.6. The Organizer reserves the sole right to alter the allocated exhibit space position if deemed necessary and in the best interest of the Exhibition in order to provide a viable layout. The Organizer’s decision on such re-allocation of exhibit space shall be final and binding on the Exhibitor.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.7. The Exhibitor covenants and agrees that all governmental and other regulatory approvals required for the display or use of Exhibition Materials and its participation at the Exhibition shall be obtained prior to the commencement of the Exhibition (including all licenses or permits that may be required to operate or conduct the Exhibition and to pay all taxes, fees and charges levied against it in connection with the Exhibition).
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.8. Subject to the Exhibition's accident prevention plan as provided to the Exhibitor by the Organizer, the Exhibitor may fit out and decorate their Booth per their discretion, provided they do not hinder the visibility of safety signs and equipment or of nearby stands and they are consistent with the overall decoration of the Exhibition. In case of materials or installations deemed to be non-compliant to the regulations and/or the laws by the Organizer, the Organizer reserves the right, at any time and at the Exhibitor's expense, to prohibit the use of the Booth and/or assigned location, to suspend the use of water and electricity or to have removed or to destroy any materials or installations deemed non-compliant by the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.9. The Organizer hereby grants to the Exhibitor a non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-assignable and non-licensable, royalty free and limited right to use and/or display the Organizer Marks for the limited purpose of associating with the Exhibition and promoting their participation in order to receive foot falls for the duration of the term.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.10. The Exhibitor shall operate and conduct its participation at the Exhibition exclusively under the Organizer 's Marks and shall feature the Organizer's Marks in all advertising matter and other promotional material, together with standard distinguishing characteristics prescribed by the Organizer  under such other than the Organizer 's  Marks as may be designated in writing and adopted by the Organizer  so that the exhibition conducted on the Venue displaying an Exhibitor/s products will be directly recognizable by the general public.

<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.11. The Organizer has intimated to the Exhibitor in writing regarding the rules and regulations which govern this association between the Parties and the manner in which the Exhibition is conducted. A copy of the said Policy can be accessed at www.hivefurnitureshow.com The Exhibitor acknowledges and agrees that the Exhibitor has read and reviewed the Organizer policy to adhere with the same.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.12. The Exhibitor covenants and agrees:
<br></br>
<br></br>
      <p style="margin-left:45px">
           2.12.1. to observe and comply with the reasonable directions of the Organizer.

          <br></br>
          <br></br>
            2.12.2. to be and remain in the care, custody, and control of the Exhibition Material
<br></br>
<br></br>
            2.12.3. to refrain from any Objectionable Display and forthwith remove and clear any Objectionable Displays, as may be required by Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
            2.12.4. not to use the Exhibition for any immoral, improper, unlawful or illegal purpose or a manner that is likely to cause public disorder in or near the Centre, or in way that might cause harm to any persons or damage to the property of the Organizer or the Centre Users, or in a way so as to cause nuisance or annoyance to the Centre User;
<br></br>
<br></br>
            2.12.5. not to unless permitted in writing by the Organizer and then only in accordance with any conditions imposed, collect any charges or fees for admission to the exhibit space;
<br></br>
<br></br>
            2.12.6. not to install or exhibit any Objectionable Displays:
<br></br>
<br></br>
            2.12.7. observe and comply with Applicable Laws.

      </p>

<br></br>
<br></br>
        2.13. Save and except as otherwise agreed in writing between the Exhibitors and Organizer, the Exhibitor shall not be entitled to grant any third party the right to use and exhibit at the Booth (either the whole or any part of the exhibit space). For the avoidance of doubt, the Exhibitor may only be allowed to share a Booth subject to (a) the Organizer’s prior written approval for the exhibit space to be shared; and (b) if approved by the Organizer in writing, the Exhibitor shall introduce such third person to Organizer for them to do a direct participation agreement. It is agreed that should the Exhibitor violate this provision; the Organizer shall have the unilateral right to relocate the related Booth space for any such Exhibitor(s) and/or a penalty of USD 100 per SQM will be payable by the Exhibitor. There will be no adjustment of any Total Exhibition Fees owed by such Exhibitor(s)
<br></br>
<br></br>




                                            <strong> 3. PAYMENT </strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <p style="margin-left:30px"></p>



        3.1 The Exhibitor shall pay the Total Exhibition Fee in the amount, the manner and in accordance with the invoices issued pursuant to in Schedule A.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.2 Time for payment shall be of the essence of the Agreement. Late payments shall be subject to interest payment calculated at monthly EIBOR rate by Emirates NBD or 5% P.A. whichever is higher and calculated from the due date to the date of receipt of the entire amount (that is, the outstanding amount and the interest amount thereon).
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.3 No payment shall be deemed to have been received until the Organizer has received cleared funds.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.4 All outstanding payments owed to the Organizer on account of the Total Exhibition Fee shall become due immediately on cancellation or termination of the Agreement without prejudice to any other rights reserved under this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.5 The Total Exhibition Fee for the exhibition is exclusive of any applicable bank charges which are to be borne by the Exhibitor.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.6 The Total Exhibition Fee is payable in full even if the Exhibitor for any reason does not utilize the exhibit space or any part thereof.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.7 The Total Exhibition Fee stated in the Participation Agreement are exclusive of any applicable taxes, all amounts expressed to be payable under this Agreement by Exhibitor to the Organizer which (in whole or part) constitute the consideration for any supply for VAT purposes are deemed to be exclusive of any VAT which is chargeable on any supply made by Organizer to the Exhibitor under this Agreement and the Organizer is required to account to the relevant tax authority for the VAT, the Exhibitor shall pay to the Organizer (in addition to and at the same time as paying any other consideration for such supply) an amount equal to the amount of the VAT, and the Organizer shall provide an appropriate VAT invoice to the Exhibitor. 5% VAT is applicable on Services and Goods in UAE since Jan 01, 2018 as per Federal Decree Law No. 8, 2017.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.8 Any additional services and amenities bought before, during or after fair will be invoiced separately, on which VAT will be applicable.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        3.9 Any part payment shall not entitle the Exhibitor any Booth space or participation at the Exhibition. The Exhibitor further undertakes that once this Agreement is executed between the Exhibitor and the Organizer, the Exhibitor is liable to make payments in full within 7 (seven) days of the Organizer raising the invoice as per the Total Exhibition Fee. In the event full applicable payment is not received by the Organizer within the said 7 (seven) days, there shall be no grace period and the Organizer retains the right to re-allocate the same Booth and/or offer the same Offerings to another exhibitor or third party and this defaulting Exhibitor shall have no right, title, interest or claims with regard to the said Booth, the Organizer, or the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
                                        </p>




                                            <strong>
                                                4. CANCELLATION
                                            </strong>
                                            <p style="margin-left:30px">
    <br></br>
        4.1 The Exhibitor shall immediately inform the Organizer in writing of its intention not to utilize the exhibit Participation Agreement. In the event that no notice is provided whatsoever to the Organizer hereunder, the Exhibitor shall indemnify the Organizer for all cost associated with its non-compliance with this provision (including loss of profit and consequential losses).
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.2 Upon receipt of written notice under clause 4.1 (but subject to clause 4.7)
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.3 All rights granted to the Exhibitor pursuant to the Agreement shall cease and the Organizer shall be at liberty to enter and use the exhibit space.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.4 All sums paid to the Organizer by the Exhibitor on account of the Total Exhibition Fee shall be forfeited to the Organizer, and the Exhibitor shall pay in full any portion outstanding of the Total Exhibition Fee and other outstanding amounts then owed to the Organizer on account of the Total Exhibition Fee forthwith.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.5 Subject to clause 4.4, 4.5 and 4.6 the Organizer reserves the right at all times to change the date of the Exhibition. In relation to its commencement, duration and conclusion, or to cancel due to Force Majeure.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.6 If the Exhibition is substantively postponed by the Organizer the amount of the Total Exhibition Fee paid by the Exhibitor shall be carried over in view of the Exhibitor’s participation in the postponed Exhibition. For the avoidance of doubt, any credit note issued/carry over shall only be valid for the next annual show edition (unless otherwise agreed between the parties) Thereafter the credit note/carry over and the amount of the Total Exhibition Fee paid by the Exhibitor for the Exhibition shall be forfeited to the Organizer in the event the postponed Exhibition dates are not suitable for the Exhibitor.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.7 In the event of the cancellation of the Exhibition by the Organizer without cause the Exhibitor shall be entitled to a refund, within a reasonable time, of the Total Exhibition Fee paid to the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.8 If the Exhibition is cancelled due to Force Majeure the Exhibitor shall be entitled to a refund in an amount equal to the Total Exhibition Fee already paid to the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.9 In the event that the Exhibitor cancelled its participation in the Exhibition as a result of it being impossible for the Exhibitor to attend due to borders being completely closed and a full lock-down in place; then in such circumstances the Exhibitor shall be entitled to a full refund in an amount equal to the Exhibition Fee already paid to the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        4.10 In the event of the cancellation or postponement of the Exhibition underclause 4, the Exhibitor shall assume all risk associated with the non-occurrence or delay of the Exhibition and in particular, the Exhibitor alone shall bear all cost the Exhibitor may have chosen to incur in anticipation of the Exhibition.
                                            </p>

                                                     <strong>
                                                             5. REDUCTION OF EXHIBIT SPACE

                                                     </strong>

                                            <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                     <br></br>
                                                     <br></br>

        5.1 All requests for reduction of exhibit space must be made in writing to the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        5.2 If the written request in clause 5.1 for reduction is received by the Organizer up until twelve (12) weeks before the Exhibition, the Organizer may in its absolute discretion, allow for the reduction, otherwise any written requests for reduction received by the Organizer after this period shall not be accepted.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        5.3 The Total Exhibition Fee is payable in full even if the Organizer agrees to reduce the exhibit space.
    <br></br>
    <br></br>
                                            </p>

                                                                                    <strong>

    6. STAND BOUNDARIES</strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <p style="margin-left:30px">

        6.1 All Exhibition Materials must be kept within the agreed boundaries of the Exhibitor’s exhibited spaced at all times. No exhibitors may obstruct the gangways with the Exhibition Materials, nor may any such Exhibition Materials protrude from the boundaries of the exhibit space. All distribution of literature must take place within the boundaries of the Exhibitor’s exhibit space and not in the gangways or any other area within the Venue. Any Exhibitor who continues to cause a nuisance or obstruction after notice has been given will be liable to have their exhibit space cleared by the Organizer at the Exhibitor’s own risk and expense.
                                                <br></br>
                                            </p>

                                            <strong>
    7. WARRANTY </strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>



        7.1 The Exhibitor represent, warrants and undertakes that it is entering into this Agreement as principal and not as agent or nominee of any third party, and that the Exhibition Materials do not infringe or is likely to infringe any patent, trademark, copyrights or any other Intellectual Property Right of any party. Also agrees that in the event of any breach of representation, warranties and undertakings herein contained this Agreement may be terminated by the Organizer and the Exhibitor shall indemnify the Organizer against any and all cost claims, demands, losses, termination due to the Exhibitor’s breach.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.2 Good title: The Exhibitor has the full power and absolute authority to enter into this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.3 No Disability: The Exhibitor is not under any disability, restriction, or prohibition, whether legal, contractual, or otherwise, which shall prevent the Exhibitor from performing or adhering to any of their obligations under this Agreement, and the Exhibitor has not entered and shall not enter into any agreement that may violate this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.4 Litigation: No litigation, arbitration, or administrative proceedings are threatened, or to the knowledge of the Exhibitor, pending, which call into question the validity or performance of their obligations under this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.5 Compliance with Applicable Laws: The Exhibitor will perform its obligations under this Agreement and make sales to the end consumer in compliance with all Applicable Laws.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.6 The Exhibitor shall provide such cooperation as the Organizer reasonably requests in order to give full effect to the provisions of this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.7 The Exhibitor has the requisite expertise, experience, infrastructure, manpower, mobility and communication modes required to efficiently perform the obligations under the present Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.8 The Exhibitor specifically represents and warrants that the Exhibitor is not employing any pirated or unauthorized software of any description for any purposes whatsoever and/or is not in violation of Intellectual Property Rights of any third party.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.9 Neither this Agreement nor any schedule or annexure hereto, contains any untrue statement of a material fact or omits to state a material fact necessary to make the statements herein or therein misleading.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        7.10 The Exhibitor acknowledges that it has conducted an independent investigation of the business venture hereunder and recognizes that the business venture contemplated by this Agreement involves business risks and that its success will be largely dependent upon the ability of the Exhibitor as an independent business and/or businessman. The Organizer expressly disclaims the making of, and the Exhibitor acknowledges that it has not received from the Organizer, their agents and representation, inducement, warranty or guarantee, express or implied, as to the potential volume profits, or success of the business venture contemplated by this Agreement.

    <br></br>
    <br></br>

  <strong>8. SOUND LEVEL</strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>
<p style="margin-left:30px">
            8.1 The sound level of audio equipment must be tuned to an acceptable volume and conducted in a way that does not interfere with or becomes a nuisance to neighboring exhibitors. The Organizer reserves the right to monitor and where necessary, determine the acceptable level of sound for equipment entertainment and audio-visual presentations. If the Exhibitor continues to refuse to comply with the request to reduce the volume, the Organizer reserves the right to disconnect all power supplies to the exhibit space and no compensation will be made to the Exhibitor.

</p>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>


  <strong> 9. EXHIBITOR’S RESPONSIBILITY</strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>
<p style="margin-left:30px">

        9.1 The Exhibitor is responsible for all claims, actions or cost for personal injury and loss of or damage to property caused by or arising from the erection or dismantling of the stands and anything permitted, committed or done during the period  of the Exhibition including the build-up or tear-down periods, caused by the Exhibitor or any of its contractors, sub- contractor, agents, or the act, omission or neglect of or by any such person, or by any Exhibition Material or other article belonging to or in the care, control or custody of the Exhibitor. The Exhibitor shall comply with all the requirements of the Exhibitor Manual and ensure the contractor and sub-contractor and suppliers likewise comply with its provisions.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.2 The Exhibitor will set up a Booth adhering to the specifications provided by the Organizer regarding the format and size of the display to be used for branding by the Exhibitor. For each Booth the Exhibitor is obligated to obtain the fit-out services from the Organizer or its designees. The Exhibitor agrees and acknowledges to comply with the fit-out requirements provided by the Organizer. In the event the Exhibitor desires to engage a third party to obtain fit out services for the Booth, then the Exhibitor shall be permitted to engage third party services only after the Organizer ’s written approval (email permitted). The Exhibitor shall make sure that the third party strictly complies with the fit our requirements and/or specifications provided by the Organizer. Whatever design the Exhibitor might want to use will have to be approved by the Organizer and then the Exhibitor can execute basis the Organizer’s approval–This can be done by the Organizer or Organizer’s approved vendor.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.3 The Organizer shall provide to the details and the dimensions of the space to be allocated to an Exhibitor on the Venue. All costs in relation to the fit out of the Booth to conduct the Exhibition including but not limited to civil work, electrical work, lightening, UPS, MEP, painting, labour charges, CCTV camera, charges for hiring the truck, crane etc. shall be borne by the Exhibitor alone.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.4 The Exhibitor shall build and demarcate the Booths strictly in accordance with the site criteria given by the Organizer. The Organizer shall have the right to supervise and inspect the fit-out work to ensure that the Venue and all Booths are ready as per the fit-out requirements.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.5 Exhibitor shall be responsible for any additional costs associated with the Exhibition, including but not limited to utilities, cleaning, security, insurance, damage and any special requests or services required by the Exhibitor.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.6 The Exhibitor will be solely responsible for any payments to be collected from the customer towards the sale of the products being sold by the Exhibitor at the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.7 The Exhibitor shall be solely responsible for promptly and properly dismantling and removing the Booth at the end of the Exhibition Day.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.8 The Exhibitor acknowledges and agrees that the space provided for the Booth is solely for exhibiting furniture products during the Exhibition. The Exhibitor shall not, assign, or share the allotted Booth space without prior written consent from the Organizer. Any stand changes/ enhancements/revisions costs are to be borne by Exhibitor for which the payment (with taxes) will be made to the Organizer by the Exhibitor before setting up dates of the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.9 The Exhibitor shall not use the Organizer Marks and/or Organizer Deliverables and/or the Intellectual Property of the Organizer otherwise than as agreed upon and permitted under this Agreement and/or use the same with any other Intellectual Property of any other party and/or not alter, modify or reproduce any Organizer Marks in any manner not specifically provided for in this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.10 The Exhibitor shall not use any Intellectual Property of the Organizer or the Organizer Marks in or on billboards, radio, motion pictures or television except as expressly approved by the Organizer in writing, and//or in any manner not specifically provided for in the Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.11 The Exhibitor shall not do any act and/ or make any statements or cause to be done any act and/ or cause to be made any statements which are prejudicial to the reputation and status of the Organizer, the Exhibition and/ or the guests performing and/or attending the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.12 The Exhibitor is not to disclose, reveal or make public except with the prior written consent of the Organizer, any information whatsoever concerning the Organizer and/or the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.13 The Exhibitor shall adhere to the Brand usage guidelines as provided by the Organizer from time to time and all material containing the Organizer Marks shall be sent to the Organizer for prior written approval before publication / release to third parties.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        9.14 The Exhibitor undertakes and certifies that the materials, products to be presented at the Exhibition are not, and are not liable to be, the subject of a dispute that could lead to a seizure during the Exhibition or more generally any damage for the Organizers and managers of the venues in which the event is taking place.
<br></br>
<br></br>
</p>

  <strong>
    10. EXHIBITORS AND PASSES</strong>

<p style="margin-left:30px">

<br></br>
<br></br>
        10.1 Every exhibitor shall ensure their exhibit space is open to view and staﬀed by competent representatives during the Exhibition opening hours. In the event of any exhibitor failing to open their exhibit space or uncover their Exhibition Material, then the Organizer may do so or may arrange for the exhibit space and Exhibition Materials to be removed, and the Exhibitor shall be liable for any charges that may be incurred. The Organizer will not be liable for any damage, losses, or expenses sustained by the Exhibitor as a result of this action.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        10.2 Every exhibitor and all persons for whom they may be considered responsible in any way whatsoever must conduct themselves in such a manner as shall not be objectionable to any other exhibitor, visitor or the Organizer. The Exhibitor shall observe the traditions and social norms applicable in the UAE.
Any person who does not comply with these requirements shall be liable, at the discretion of the Organizer to be immediately removed from the Exhibition and refused re-admission during the period of the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        10.3 The Exhibitor will be allotted a Booth at the Exhibition by the Organizer. For this purpose, the Organizer shall onboard each Exhibitor in accordance with the process detailed herein. The Organizer will provide an Exhibitor a direct access to its online portal. The Organizer will also provide the Exhibitor with a unique user ID and password to be able to easily log into its online portal on its official webpage. Pursuant to the log-in, the Exhibitor will be required to fill in a form to register all the details of its Organizer for the Exhibition. The form will be displayed on the dashboard of the Organizer 's online portal. The Exhibitor shall complete the Exhibitor onboarding process for the Exhibition at least 45 days before the Exhibition. Thereafter, the Organizer shall issue oﬃcial passes for the admission to the Exhibition and no other form for admission pass shall be valid. No Exhibitor shall be admitted to the Exhibition without producing to the gate oﬃcial the Exhibitor’s pass being transferred or otherwise disposed of it shall be immediately forfeited and no further pass will be issued in its place.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        10.4 The Organizer reserves the right at their sole discretion to withdraw the pass issued to any person if complaints have been received concerning his/ her conduct or if there has been a breach of this Agreement.
<br></br>
<br></br>
</p>




    <strong> 11. ORGANIZER’S RIGHT OF ENTRY </strong>
                                            <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                        11.1 The Organizer and those authorized by them have the right to enter the premises of the Exhibition at any time to execute works, repairs, and alterations and for any other purposes deemed necessary. No compensation shall be payable to an exhibitor for damage, loss or inconvenience so caused.

                                            </p>







    <strong> 12. MANDATORY SHOW INSURANCE, MARKETING POWERPACK, REGISTRATION FEE, ENHANCED INTERNET LISTING AND LEAD GENERATION &amp; TRACKING.</strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <p style="margin-left:30px">

        12.1 The Exhibitor shall carry insurance to cover the following risk (a) Public Liability for USD 2.72 million; (b) Fire Damage for USD 57000; (c) Medical; Expenses for USD 1360 per person; (d)Food and drink Poisoning for USD 2.72 million. (e) Damage caused by the Exhibitor to exhibition venue property for USD 2.72 million (f)Liability arising out of loading and unloading of Exhibition Materials; (g) Exhibitor to Exhibitor Liability for USD 2.72 Million; (h) Liability due to erection and dismantling of stands; (i) Damage caused to the Exhibitor’s property for USD 13600 (k) Personal Accident (Including death and disability) For 3 employees of the Exhibitors for USD 8170 per employee. The Cover must be provided by, and insurance company registered in UAE. The Exhibitor will be responsible for ﬁling and setting any claims under the policy directly with the insurance company.
<br></br>
<br></br>

        12.2 The insurance cover prescribed in clause 12.1 will be taken out by the organizer and the insurance cost charged to the Exhibitor, which shall be paid in the amount, the manner and in accordance with the invoice issued pursuant to Schedule A. Any policy of insurance obtained by the Exhibitor shall be acceptable only if complies with all the requirements of clause 12.1 and provided proof or certiﬁcate of such cover along with the policy terms and conditions are submitted to the Organizer at least two months prior to the commencement of build-up for the Exhibition.

<br></br>
<br></br>


</p>

   <strong> 13. ADVERTISING AND PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES </strong>
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>

        13.1 The Organizer reserves the exclusive right to post advertising and other marketing materials and operate promotions in the Venue where the Exhibition is held and in the immediate surrounding area.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        13.2 The Exhibitor shall procure prior written permission from the Organizer in relation to all advertising and promotional material proposed to be used by the Exhibitor in relation to the Exhibition. The Exhibitor acknowledges and agrees that unless otherwise agreed to between the parties all forms of advertisement shall be strictly limited to the Exhibitor Booth. In the event of non-compliance with these requirements, the Organizer may remove such advertising at any time without prior notice. The Exhibitor shall not in any form whatsoever display products or services or advertise companies or businesses who are not participants to the Exhibition, without the Organizer ’s prior written authorization.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        13.3 The Exhibitor warrants and confirms that the Organizer shall have the right to record and photograph the event with or without sound (including spoken words, dialogue and music synchronously recorded), use components of the Booth’s wholly or partially, make and/or authorize others to make any documentary film on the making of the Exhibition. The Exhibitor acknowledges that such documentary film may include footage of so-called behind the scenes activities and may incorporate extracts or clips from the Exhibition. The Exhibitor irrevocably consents to the use by the Organizer of such outtakes and other material featuring the Exhibitor and the Exhibitor employees in such documentary film and/or any other audio-visual production and confirm that the Organizer shall have the right to exploit any and all of the foregoing in any and all media by any and all manner or means in perpetuity throughout the universe for no additional consideration.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        13.4 The Organizer shall have the right to prohibit the taking of photographs and/or the making of audio and video recordings by the employees of the Exhibitor who have not received accreditation from the Organizer for such purpose. Only photographers/ cameramen who have received written authorization from the Organizer for such purpose shall be allowed to operate a camera within the Venue.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        13.5 The Exhibitor acknowledges and agrees that the Organizer shall be free to enter any participation arrangement with any third parties in relation to the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        13.6 Nothing contained herein gives or transfers or assigns or is intended to give or transfer or assign any right, title or interest of any nature whatsoever to or in respect of the Organizer Marks of the Organizer to the Exhibitor. The Exhibitor shall have no right or license pertaining to use the Organizer Marks and or any names or intellectual property of the Venue.
<br></br>
<br></br>


                                        </p>




  <strong>14. TERMINATION </strong>
<br></br>
<br></br>
        14.1 The Organizer may take possession of the exhibit space and terminate this Agreements forthwith by written notice to the Exhibitor upon the Exhibitor’s failure to meet any of their obligations under the terms and conditions of this Agreement and the Exhibitor Manual, including but not limited to the Exhibitor’s: (a)failure to pay for the Total Exhibition Fee or any related services within 7 calendar days of written notice. (b) failure to set up its Exhibition Material in the exhibit space as per the terms and conditions herein. (c) failure to own and maintain valid rights to make, use, perform, sell and display patented products, copyrighted works, trademarks and trade names; or (d) Violation of any patents, copyright or other Intellectual Property Rights of another exhibitor or third party in any Exhibition Materials or (e) involvement in the selling and/ or promotion of any counterfeit or illegal goods at the Exhibition including goods that, in the sole opinion of the Organizer, do not conform to the permitted show profile of the Exhibition.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        14.2 Upon the termination of this Agreement:
<br></br>
                                        <p style="margin-left:45px">
                                                 14.2.1. any rights granted to the Exhibitor under this Agreement shall immediately terminate;
                                            <br></br>
                                            <br></br>

            14.2.2. the Exhibitor shall immediately cease to use the Organizer ’s Marks and any advertising and promotional material created pursuant to this Agreement;
<br></br>
<br></br>
            14.2.3. the Organizer and the Exhibitor shall within commercially reasonable time return to the other all property of the other in its possession.
<br></br>
<br></br>
                                        </p>

        14.3 The Organizer  shall not be required to refund any portion of the Total Exhibition Fee already received by the Organizer towards Booth set-up cost if necessary, to remove and dispatch such exhibits (at the risk and expense of the Exhibitors) and apply this to the recovery of any monies owed to the Organizer on account of the Total Exhibition Fee shall be forfeited and the Exhibitor shall pay any outstanding amount owed to the Organizer on account of the Total Exhibition Fee forthwith in addition, the Organizer reserves the right to claim any loss or damages, established by the Organizer or arising out of such Termination.


<br></br>
<br></br>

  <strong>  15. BANKRUPCY OR LIQUIDATION </strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
<br></br>
<br></br>
        15.1 In the event of an Exhibitor becoming bankrupt or entering into liquidation (other than voluntary liquidation for the purpose of amalgamation or reconstruction) or having a receiver appointed, this Agreement will terminate forthwith, the allotment of exhibit space will be cancelled, and all sums paid by the Exhibitor to the Organizer on account of the Total Exhibition Fee under the Agreements shall be forfeited.
<br></br>
<br></br>
        15.2 In the event of the Organizer becomes bankrupt or enters into liquidation (other than voluntary liquidation for the purpose of amalgamation or reconstruction), or has a receiver appointed, this Agreement will terminate forthwith, and no further fees will be payable by the Exhibitor to the Organizer.
<br></br>
<br></br>
                                        </p>
 <strong>  16. FORCE MAJEURE </strong>
                                        <br></br>
                                        <br></br>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    16.1 The Organizer and the Exhibitor shall not be in breach of this Agreement nor be liable for any failure or delay in performance of any obligations thereunder arising from or attributable to an event of Force Majeure (with the exception of payment obligations) provided that such party has promptly notified the other party in writing of the nature and extent of the event of Force Majeure causing its failure or delay in performance. If an event of Force Majeure occurs and written notice is served then the Organizer may terminate this Agreement by written notice and the provisions of Clause 4.6 above shall apply. In the event of termination of this Agreement pursuant to Force Majeure, neither party shall be liable to the other for any loss or damage of any nature or kind whatsoever suﬀered as a result of such termination.

                                        </p>
                                        <br></br>
                                        <br></br>


   <strong>17. ASSIGNMENT  </strong>
<p style="margin-left:30px">
            17.1 The Exhibitor may not assign or transfer any of its rights or obligations under the Agreement without the prior written approval of the Organizer. The Organizer may assign the whole or any part of this Agreement to any third party without the consent of, but with notice to, the Exhibitor. This Agreement shall be binding on the successors -in tittle of the respective parties.

</p>
<br></br>
<br></br>


                                     <strong>  18. CONFIDENTIALITY</strong>

                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                18.1 The parties shall always treat this Agreement as private and confidential and its contents shall not be disclosed either directly or indirectly to any person except with the prior written approval of the other party; or as may be required by any statutory, regulatory, or governmental or quasi government authority, or as otherwise required by law.

                                        </p>
<br></br>
<br></br>

  <strong> 19. SEVERABILITY </strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    19.1 If any term or conditions of the Agreement or the application thereof to any person or circumstances shall to any extent be invalid or unenforceable, the remainder of the Agreement, or application of such term or condition to persons or circumstances other than those as to which is it held invalid or unenforceable shall not be aﬀected thereby and each term or condition of the contract shall be valid and enforceable.

                                        </p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<strong>     20. INDEMNITY </strong>
<p style="margin-left:30px">
    <br></br>
    <br></br>
      20.1 The Exhibitor hereby indemniﬁes and agrees to keep the Organizer indemnified against;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        20.2 Any and all, proceeding, claim, cost, damages or losses incurred of suﬀered by the Organizer by reason of breach by the Exhibition of this Agreement, any regulation, or any applicable law, or for any act, or omission on the part of the Exhibitor whatsoever and/or any unauthorized use of the Exhibitor Brand by the Exhibitor or any copyright infringement claims regarding the Brand;
<br></br>
<br></br>
        20.3 Any and all customs, levy, tax ﬁne, or other payment the Organizer is called upon to pay any authorities on behalf of the Exhibitor in relation of the Exhibition.


</p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
    <strong>
            21. ORGANIZER’S LIABILITY

    </strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    21.1 The Organizer will not be liable to the Exhibitor or any third party for any loss of proﬁts or business, or for any direct or consequential loss or damage. The total liability of the Organizer to the Exhibitor arising out of or in connection with this Agreement will not exceed the amount of the Total Exhibition Fee actually paid by the Exhibitor under this Agreement.

                                        </p>
<br></br>
    <strong>  22. WAIVER</strong>

                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    22.1 The Exhibitor waived any and all claims (of whatsoever nature) that it may have against the Organizer in anyway related to the storage. display or use of any exhibit/equipment in connection with the Exhibition, whether prior to, in the course of or after its conclusion or after regular hours. The Exhibitor, acknowledges and accepts sole and exclusive responsibility for the safety and security and storage of all the property and belongings of the Exhibitor at all times.

                                        </p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
   <strong> 23. ENTIRE AGREEMENT </strong>
      <p style="margin-left:30px">
                  23.1 These regulations together with the Participation Agreement constitute the whole agreement and understanding between the parties relating to the subject matter and supersedes any prior agreements whether in writing or oral, relating to such subject matter. No variation of this Agreement shall be effective unless made in writing and signed by each of the parties.

      </p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
    <strong> 24. NOTICES </strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    24.1 Any and all notices, demand and statements or documents of any kind that are desired or required to be given by one party to the other according to the provisions of the Agreement may be delivered by hand, and upon successful completion of the transmission, sent by fax or electronic mail. Unless and until change by notice in writing given in accordance with the clause, the addresses, fax number and electronic mail id for the parties shall be as set forth in the Agreement.

                                        </p>
                                        <br></br>
                                        <br></br>
<strong>
        25. CALENDAR

</strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    25.1 All dates and period will be determined by reference to the Gregorian Calendar.

                                        </p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
                                        <strong>
                                                26. GOVERNING LAW &amp; JURISDICTION

                                        </strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                                                    26.1 This Agreement shall be interpreted and construed in accordance with the laws applicable in Dubai, UAE. The courts of Dubai, UAE shall have exclusive jurisdiction in any matter relating to or arising out of this Agreement except for any payment related claims, courts of Dubai and /or courts of the city of the Exhibitors registered address shall have jurisdiction.

                                        </p>
 <t t-if="o.include_special_condition">


                                                                                <strong>
                                              27. SPECIAL INCLUSIONS


                                        </strong>
                                        <p style="margin-left:30px">
                        <div style="text-align:left">

        <span t-esc="o.hotel_special_inclusion_info"/>

                        </div>                                        </p>

     </t>

                                    </td>



<!--                                    COLMN 2 OF THE RECORD-->
<!--                                    colm-2-->
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
<br></br>
<br></br>

 <div style="font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold;">
<!--                            <div class="text-center" style="font-weight: 900;">-->
<!--                                <u>-->
<!--                                    <b>-->
<!--                                        SCHEDULE A-->
<!--                                        <br></br>-->
<!--                                   </b>-->
<!--                                </u>-->
<!--                            </div>-->
<!-- </div>-->
<!--                            <br/>-->
<!--The payment plan for the Rental Fee and Insurance Cost (including any applicable Marketing Powerpack Costs) (“Total Exhibition Fee”) to be paid by Exhibitor to the Organizer shall be as follows:                             <div style="font-size: 9pt; text-align: justify; font-weight: bold;">-->


<!--                            <br/>-->
<!--                            <div class="text-center" style="font-weight: 900;">-->
<!--                                <b>-->
<!--                                    SCHEDULE A-->
<!--                                </b>-->
<!--                            </div>-->
<!--     <br/>-->
<!--                            <div style="font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold; text-align: justify;">-->
<!--The payment plan for the Rental Fee and Insurance Cost (including any applicable Marketing Powerpack Costs) (“Total Exhibition Fee”) to be paid by Exhibitor to the Organizer shall be as follows:                             </div>-->

 <div style="font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold;">
                                <div class="text-center" style="font-weight: 900;">
                                    <u>
                                        <b>
                                            SCHEDULE A
                                            <br></br>
                                            Total Exhibition Fee
                                        </b>
                                    </u>
                                </div>
                                <br/>
                                Total Exhibition Fee shall be as follows:
                                <div style="font-size: 9pt; text-align: justify; font-weight: bold;">
                                    1.
                                    Booths without Offerings will be made available


                                    <t t-if="o.space_type_id.type == 'non-package'">

                                        <span style="padding-left: 10px;" t-field="o.total_unit_price"
                                              t-options='{"widget": "monetary", "display_currency": o.pricelist_id.currency_id}'/>
                                        per square meter plus applicable taxes;

                                    </t>
                                    <t t-else="o.space_type_id.type == 'non-package'">

                                        __ per square meter plus applicable taxes;

                                    </t>
                                    <br></br>
                                    2. Booths along with Offerings will be made available
                                    <t t-if="o.space_type_id.type == 'package'">

                                        <span style="padding-left: 10px;" t-field="o.total_unit_price"
                                              t-options='{"widget": "monetary", "display_currency": o.pricelist_id.currency_id}'/>
                                        per square meter plus applicable taxes.
                                    </t>

                                    <t t-else="o.space_type_id.type == 'package'">

                                        __ per square meter plus applicable taxes.
                                    </t>
                                </div>
 </div>
     <br></br>


                        <div class="text-center" style="font-weight: 900;">
                                <b>
PAYMENT TERMS                                </b>
                            </div>
     <br/>
                            <div style="font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold; text-align: justify;">

Installment of the Total Exhibition Fee as per % assigned to be received along with the signed Participation Agreement on or before the due date.                        </div>








                        </div>








                        <br/>
                        <t t-if="o.exhibitor_payment_stage_ids">
                              <div style="font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold;">
                                <t t-set="payment_sl_no" t-value="1"/>
                                <table style="width: 100%;">
                                    <thead>
                                        <tr>
                                            <th style="padding: 5px; width: 7%; border: 1px solid black;">Sl.No.</th>
                                            <th style="padding: 5px; width: 44%; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                Description
                                            </th>
                                            <th style="padding: 5px; width: 14%; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                Break up%
                                            </th>
                                            <th style="padding: 5px; width: 15%; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                Amount
                                            </th>
                                            <th style="padding: 5px; width: 20%; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                Payment Due Date
                                            </th>
                                        </tr>
                                    </thead>
                                    <tbody>
                                        <tr t-foreach="o.exhibitor_payment_stage_ids" t-as="payment">
                                            <td style="text-align: center; padding: 3px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <span t-esc="payment_sl_no"/>
                                                <t t-set="payment_sl_no" t-value="payment_sl_no+1"/>
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="text-align: left; padding: 3px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <span t-esc="payment.name"/>
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="width: 15%; text-align: center; padding: 3px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <span t-esc="int(payment.paid_percentage)"/>%
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="width: 15%; text-align: center; padding: 3px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <span t-esc="payment.paid_amount"
                                                      t-options='{"widget": "monetary", "display_currency": o.pricelist_id.currency_id}'/>
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="width: 20%;  text-align: center; padding: 3px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <t t-if="payment.payment_due_date">
                                                    <span t-esc="payment.payment_due_date.strftime('%d-%B-%Y').upper()"/>
                                                </t>
                                            </td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td colspan="2"
                                                style="text-align: center; padding: 2px 5px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <b>Total</b>
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="text-align: center; padding: 2px 5px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <b>
                                                    <span t-esc="sum(o.exhibitor_payment_stage_ids.mapped('paid_percentage'))"/>
                                                    %
                                                </b>
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="text-align: center; padding: 2px 5px; border: 1px solid black;">
                                                <b>
                                                    <span t-esc="sum(o.exhibitor_payment_stage_ids.mapped('paid_amount'))"
                                                          t-options='{"widget": "monetary", "display_currency": o.pricelist_id.currency_id}'/>
                                                </b>
                                            </td>
                                            <td style="text-align: center; padding: 2px 5px; border: 1px solid black;"/>
                                        </tr>
                                    </tbody>
                                </table>
                            </div>
                        </t>





          <div>
              <div>
                  <br></br>


                  Non-compliance with this schedule may lead to the cancellation of your booking, with any partial payments made being non-refundable.


                  <br></br>
                  <br></br>
                  <div class="col-6"></div>
                  <div class="col-6" style="margin-left:65%">

                       <img src="/techfuge_exhibitor_customisation/static/src/img/sign_of_owner.jpg" style="width: 250px;width:250px"/>

                  </div>
<!--                        <table style="width: 100%; line-height: 1.4; font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold;">-->
<!--                            <tbody>-->
<!--                                <tr>-->
<!--                                    <td>-->

<!--                                    </td>-->
<!--                                    <td rowspan="3" style="padding: 5px; border: 1px solid black;">-->
<!--                                        <br/>-->
<!--<br></br>-->

<!--                                        <img src="/techfuge_exhibitor_customisation/static/src/img/sign_of_owner.jpg" style="width: 250px;width:250px"/>-->



<!--                                    </td>-->

<!--                                </tr>-->
<!--                            </tbody>-->
<!--                        </table>-->
                    </div>
                </div>


<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

   <div style="font-size: 9pt; font-weight: bold;">
                                <t t-if="o.include_special_condition_section_b">
                                    <div class="text-center" style="font-weight: 900;">
                                        <u>
                                            <b>
                                                SCHEDULE B
                                                <br></br>
                                                <br></br>
                                                Offerings
                                            </b>
                                        </u>
                                    </div>
                                    <br/>

                        <div style="text-align:left">
                                                                <span t-esc="o.special_section_b"/>

                        </div>
                                </t>
                            </div>




















      </template>
   </data>
</odoo>